realore.com 2016-08-11

# Privacy polycy

We at Realore (“Realore”) have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. **By  visiting Realore, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

### INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT

#### Personally Identifiable Information:

We may collect the following information when you sign up for a service: 

  * First name, last name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number.
  * Credit or debit card information, depending on your form of payment. We do not store any credit card information after your transaction is complete.

#### IP Address:

When a user visits any Web site owned or operated by Realore, we may collect the IP address that requested the display of one of our sites.

#### Sign Up and Survey information:

Any information you provide to us as part of your use of any Realore Web site will be stored as entered.

#### Cookies:

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from Realore is only accessible by the Realore Web sites. Personal information stored in our cookies is encrypted and limited to your e-mail address and username.

#### Other Information Collected:

The Web browser or client software that you use to access Realore may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may also track other types of information, such as what games users play, how long our users have been members of any Realore businesses or programs, the last time a user visited Realore, and whether a user has won any of our games, sweepstakes or contests.

### SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

Realore takes all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data. All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through our Web sites. Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our company, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to personnel who have a need to know such information to perform their essential job functions. All employees of Realore are legally bound by a nondisclosure agreement that prevents the disclosure of any corporate or customer information to other parties.

### USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We use your username, e-mail address, and password to uniquely identify you as a user on any Realore Web site. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, chat identification, and/or game high scores.

We may use your contact information to process our newsletters and/or e-mail campaigns. Your contact information will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, sweepstakes, contests, prizes, and/or special events.

If you participate in our “Tell a friend” feature, your e-mail and IP addresses will be shared with the person to whom you send a game to using this feature. We may also use an IP address to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Service.

We use cookies to enhance your online experience. The information in cookies enables us to run our affiliate programs, enables you to automatically sign in when you visit a Realore Web site, and offers other operational site activities.

We may use other identifying information collected to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes.

### SHARING INFORMATION

We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries of Realore that follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

We will not share your information with any third parties, except that we may disclose your personal information to third parties who perform services for us, such as third-party credit card processors or prize fulfillment entities. We do not control the activities of such third-party vendors. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Realore, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information. We may also disclose your information if there is a violation of the Terms of Use or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it. Realore may provide other aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our user community to partners with whom we do business.

As Realore continues to grow, we might sell or buy certain business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy (unless you consent otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Realore or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information would in most cases be one of the transferred assets.

Apart from what is described above, you will receive notice when information about you might otherwise go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share that information.

### E-MAIL/OPT-OUT

When you create a customer account with Realore, you are automatically registered to receive one or more of our newsletters, even if you previously opted out of receiving newsletters at the time you downloaded any game for free trial play. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving these newsletters by selecting the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any newsletter. Realore treats each of its consumer offerings inpidually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one area of our website, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each such area inpidually.

### LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES

Web sites that link to or from a Realore Web site may collect personal information about you. This Realore Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other Web sites.

### CHAT & MESSAGING

Realore Web sites may operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each another. When posting to a message board or chat area, the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the inpidual user.

### CHILDREN

We at Realore do not offer products for purchase by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under 13, you may use and access the Realore Web sites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Realore respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Realore, he or she can contact us via e-mail at support@realore.com. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13\. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children’s use of online activities regularly.

### CONTACT US

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at [support@realore.com](mailto:support@realore.com).

### AGREEMENT WITH REALORE POLICIES

By using any of the Realore Web sites, products or services, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use any of the Realore Web sites, products, or services.
